Вот это поворот: оказалось, что наш Лидер — президент студсовета.
Хм? Насколько я помню, её отец…
один из школьных...
У-му, он из совета директоров.
В натуре? Так ты из богатой семьи?!
Нет, я бы не сказала.
Нашей семье всего то и принадлежит парочка заводов да школ.
Господа, я горю.
Вон оно чё.
Ну раз ты из богатеньких,
понятно.
Стапе. Те деньги, что я трачу в игре, я зарабатываю самостоятельно.
Я позаимствовала стартовый капитал у родителей, но уже вернула его.
Ах. People who are promised
a fortune in the future
can all just die.
Спокойствие, только спокойствие, Ако.
Проши прощения. Мне снесло кукушечку.
But you know, I kind of had the same reaction.
Oh, yeah?
It's a pretty strict home.
They even control who I can make friends with,
but I convinced my parents
to let me play net games.
And as a result, I got to know all of you,
but I don't have a single... real-life friend.
Master! Let's go and fight
those normies together!
Ako, you are my pal!
It pains my heart just watching them.
I never wanted to see that kind of handclasp.
"LV. 02: I thought we couldn't
play net games at school?"
To sum up,
the most important thing
is having a powerful weapon.
Spending money to buff
your armor is inefficient.
Oh, no, armor is important.
The hurdles required for choosing your
armor are higher than for weapons.
It's more efficient to level your firepower,
and go to high-level grinding spots.
And how many times has that ended up
painfully for me, "your bad self"?
Wha--? I told you not to say that!
No, I will say it! I daresay it!
Now, hold on, you guys.
There's a simpler, more perfect
way to do this. And that's--
You stay out of this, you wallet warrior!
What an awful way to treat your Master.
Listen here. If I were to spend money,
it would be on appearance.
I can leave everything alone,
and the rest of you will kill everything.
Listen, seriously, screw you.
I will knock you down.
Ako is our healer, so I can agree
with her opinion on defensive gear.
But then, Rusian dies before I can heal him.
Just so you know, as the
main tank, I can hold my own.
Our healer sucks at her job,
which is why armor is so important.
I won't deny anything about that.
Mm-hmm, there's no room for debate there.
Ah! I can't hear you!
So, um, listen... I'm sorry.
[ж.д станция Маегасаки]
Why are you apologizing?
Well, to be honest,
I thought all of you were guys!
Oh, is that all?
Huh?
I told you I was a high school girl in real life,
and you didn't believe me in the least.
When we first met up, you made
a hell of a face, you know.
That's mostly because of you.
I always figured that games
and reality were separate,
but I really did enjoy actually meeting you all.
It's like, wow, my pals in the game
are great in real life, too.
Lame. Not to mention gross.
Isn't that a bit mean?
In both the game and in real life,
my reactions are the same.
Hey, I'm in no position to point fingers.
There was part of me that wondered
whether Rusian was the kind of guy
who would leer at a girl. So we're even.
However...
...if you try to act chummy with me
at school, you'll get no mercy.
Усёк?
Усёк.
Красавчег.
А-Ако?
You don't have to be jealous;
I'm not out to steal your husband.
--I wouldn't want him.
--How rude!
До встречи.
Ах.
Русиян, ты ведь думал, что никакая я не девушка?
Прости, но я был уверен, что ты — потный качок.
Ну ты чо? Сказала же, что я девочка. И ты мне не поверил?
П-прости.
Но раз ты так думал, почему тогда согласился жениться на мне?
Мужики fine too.
Что?!
Не-не-не, я не в том смысле!
Игры и реальность не имеют ничего общего, поэтому...!
Even if you were a guy in real life,
in the game, you're still Ako,
so I thought, why not?
So um, what you're saying is,
age, looks, gender, and all that didn't matter,
and you were just nice enough...
...to start liking me, is that it?
Да, именно так.
Аналогично!
I wanted to be with you
because you are Rusian!
Even if Rusian wasn't a boy
the same age as me,
or whoever I thought you were,
I definitely, definitely...
...loved you! Инфа 100%!
Д-да. Вот спасибо, Ако.
Calm down!
Не давать волю своему либидо!
Русиян?
Вечереет! Пора по домам!
Точняк, Русиян!
Увидимся! Поки-чпоки!
О да...
Э-Это... Это...
Not too shabby, Rusian.
Leave some for my bad self, would you?
--Ako, your game is worse than usual.
--Playing like this is still the same as always...
--I-I'm doing the best I can.
--...except this happens.
Your healing can be a little bit slow,
but I don't mind at all.
Sometimes you just end up spinning
your wheels. Don't worry about it, Ako.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
I've just been losing buttloads of
EXP to death penalties, that's all.
I'm sorry, Rusian!
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Well, I think I'm about ready to log off.
I have something to handle in the morning.
At school?
Right. Being the president is usually relaxed,
but there are times when it gets busy.
Feel free to call me "Master"
if you see me at school.
I'm not doing that!
Hey, Schew, you're slipping out of character.
Y-Yeah, man.
Well, me, too.
I'm going to take a bath and go to bed.
A bath...?
What are you picturing?
Huh? No! I wasn't!
Bye, then.
Yeah, go wash off that sweat in the tub!
Like she's worked up a sweat.
--Huh?
--She's not a pig, like you, "Schwein-san."
Don't call my bad self...
Oink!
...a pig, you twerp! You really
are a pest, you know!
And here you are, associating with me.
Now that you've seen my face,
this is a lot harder to do!
It would be, huh, being a pig?
Remember, if you start acting
chummy with me at school,
I really will stick you like a pig.
I get it. I won't tell anyone,
and I won't change how I act.
You mean it?
--Oink!
--Please?
The game and reality are separate.
Also, don't act too familiar with Ako, either.
I'd hate for any funny rumors
to get started about her.
I get it, already.
Well, my bad self will log off now.
Could you pick one character and stick with it?
Oh, shut up!
З-здравия желаю... Нисимура...
И-и тебе не хворать.
Ась? Кто тебе позволил раскрывать рот в мою сторону?!
Whoa, aren't you being a bit irrational?
I see you two are getting along fine today.
H-How do I get along fine
with that disgusting guy?!
Okay, I'm sorry, Segawa. My bad.
Wait up, Akane!
Тебе тоже дали от ворот поворт?
Да десять раз.
Yeah, you've got no problem.
You've got your two-dimensional,
no-depth waifu, after all.
Mm-hmm.
Listen, my waifu is surprisingly cute,
not to mention wholeheartedly--
Попался, Русиян!
Русиян!
Что за Русиян?
Впервые слышу.
Идёт в нашу сторону.
Доброе утречко, Русиян.
Эй, Нисимура, твоя подруга?
Н-нет...
Русиян, значит, ты в классе Б.
Русиян? Это она тебе?
Нет, это... не...
Is something the matter, Rusian?
Are you not feeling well, Rusian?
Are you okay, Rusian? Rusian?!
Русиян то, Русиян сё...
Прекрати меня так называть!
И какого ты вообще хотела?!
Так ведь, прошлой ночью мы так мало были вместе.
Э?
— А-Ако, ты думаешь, что ты говоришь?
— Не заставляйте меня говорить такое,
--I-It's not like that! She doesn't
mean it that way! Really! Really!
--Rusian... It's embarrassing, isn't it?
--So, um, what is your
relationship with each other?
--Oh, Rusian, how embarrassing!
Wait! Don't answer that!
Rusian...
...is my dear husband.
Excuse me, Tamaki-san.
I don't know from Rusians and husbands,
but take that otaku talk outside, would you?
Come on, like Segawa says, let's go outside.
Ah! Schew-chan!
Schew-chan, you're in the same class
as Rusian, are you? How nice.
--Whoa, hey...
--Schew-chan?
I-I don't know what you're talking about,
but let's take it outside.
Hmm? How come?
I'm saying let's step outside.
You understand me?
Huh? Schew-chan, are you angry?
Ah, because I didn't use your full name, right?
Good morning, Schwein-san.
You aren't saying "my bad self"
and "out with it" today, are you?
N...
N...?
No!!
Take it easy, Schw-- Segawa!
You keep your mouth shut, too!
What is this? Do you three know each other?
No!
Just come with me!
Schew-chan?
Stop saying Schew-chan!
Schwein-san!
That's not what I meant!
Um, did I do something wrong?
See if you can tell me
anything you didn't do wrong!
Sch-Schew-chan, why are you upset?
Because you're calling her
"Schew" and "Schwein."
Huh? Can't I do that?
Of course not!
Listen, Ako,
"Rusian" and "Schwein" are only
our names in the game, right?
Consider the time and place.
B-But, to me, my friends
are Rusian and Schew-chan...
We're not playing the game right now.
The game and reality are separate, right?
Huh? Why is that?
Eh?
A-Ako...
What are you saying?
Did I say something strange?
Then, Schew-chan, you and I aren't friends?
After playing together for so long,
and chatting every day...
N-No, no...
L-Listen...
Rusian, are you and I strangers,
having nothing to do with each other?
But I love you, and Rusian,
you said you loved me...
You even married me...
What do we do?
She's your wife, right?
Do something about this.
For now, let's play along with her.
Okay.
Come on! Ako, you're an important
member of the guild, and our friend!
--Yeah, yeah!
--That's not true!
You're about to say something
mean about me, aren't you?!
Just like that doujin! Just like that doujin!
No, we won't.
Really?
Yeah. Ako, you're still Ako, after all.
In the game, y-you're my dear w-wife, after all.
What we mean is that we don't like
using our game names in real life.
--Being a pig and all, right?
--Oh, shut up!
At school, I'm passing as someone
who would never play games--
let alone net games.
Then, what do I call you?
You can just call me Segawa,
or Akane, like normal.
S-S-Segawa-san?
Yes, Tamaki-san.
Are we still friends?
I said we were, didn't I?
Thank goodness.
You can call me Nishimura, too.
N-Nishimura-kun...
Yeah, Ako-- I mean, Tamaki-san.
You can call me Ako.
Well, actually...
I want you to call me Ako!
Maybe once we get to be more familiar...
Then I'll just keep calling you Rusian.
I beg your pardon, Ako-san!
This is why I love you, Rusian!
I-It's Nishimura, remember?
--Wimp.
--Shut up!
Um, Schew-ch-- Segawa-san,
I can talk to you, too, right?
Sure, but no talking about net games, okay?
I can't agree to that.
Why not?
Well, there's nothing else to talk about.
Doesn't that sound sad?
Well, we can always talk all you want
in the evening while gaming.
Have your husband pick up
the slack in the meantime.
Rusian, is that okay with you?
Well, I wish you'd refrain from
the "Rusian" and husband business,
but other than that, sure.
Rusian, you really are on my side!
Did you hear what I said?
Hey, there!
Homeroom is about to begin.
It's only morning, and I'm exhausted.
Ah, Rusian, I made us lunch,
so let's have it together.
Huh? Why would you do that?
Well, Rusian, you are my husband, after all.
Yeah, but like I said,
that's just in the game, right?
Yes, we got married, right?
Nishimura, I've been thinking something...
Yeah, I think I know what you mean.
Ako... can't distinguish
between the game and real life.
"Student Council Room"
I see.
That is funny!
--It is not funny!
--It took years off my life!
I'm sorry.
No, it's nothing you have to apologize for.
She even made lunch for him.
Mm-hmm, for you,
it's only natural to make lunch
for your husband Rusian, isn't it?
Is that unusual?
Well, it's true that you and Rusian
have been together a long time, fell in love,
and at last, got married. However,
that all happened within the game.
I doubt you found love with someone
whose name and face you never knew.
That's not true! It's because I didn't know him!
Chatting with Rusian,
I came to like him because
our hearts touched each other.
It's a much, much purer love than
that of all the normies around us.
When you say it that way,
you make a good point.
Master, stand your ground.
Still, don't you find yourself not
entirely denying what she's saying?
I think Ako really does purely
like you for who you are.
But in the game, that's all jumbled together
with a character's appearances and stats, right?
On top of that, I was always looking after Ako,
so of course she thinks more of me.
It's not that.
I sometimes played the game
with people besides you, Rusian,
but they all left me right away.
But Rusian, you stuck with me the whole time.
No matter how often I goofed up,
no matter how often I forgot,
no matter how often anything...
That's why... I love you.
Yeah, okay, okay, best wishes and all that.
I'm leaving now.
Wait, Segawa! If you leave, it won't be pretty--
Don't talk to me, you hookup troll!
H-Hookup troll, you say?!
You're wrong!
You're wrong, you're wrong!
How am I wrong?
What's a hookup troll?
Someone on net games looking
for girls naive about men--
Okay, fine!
Let's do this. Let's do this, Ako.
D-Do what?
Change your mentality!
Change my mentality?
That's right! The game and reality are separate!
We're going to make you understand that!
Why would you do something so terrifying?!
Rusian, that truly is fiendish!
That's easy to say, but how?
Well, let's see...
We just have to get across
that Rusian, in the game,
and me, in real life, are two different things.
Mm-hmm, we just have to make her
realize that the game is not reality.
Master, do you have an idea?
Yeah, just leave everything to me.
"Modern Communication
Electronic Game Club"
"Modern Communication...
...Electronic Game Club"?
Sounds like a net game club, doesn't it?
Sorry.
Didn't mean to keep you waiting.
My hands were a bit full
with some application forms.
Application forms?
Hm-hm, look inside and you'll understand.
Welcome to the Modern
Communication Electronic Game Club!
That's a tad long.
The Net Game Club, for short.
I am the club president,
Goshoin Kyoh.
Fellow club members,
what do you say we take this club,
and together, get the fun started?
Net Game Club?
Club members?
Our club activities will primarily
be after-school online gaming,
and offline parties on our days off.
No way, this is too funny, right?
In what way?
What do you mean, "in what way?"
You decided on this at lunch,
you already have these computers,
and you've enrolled us into a club.
What's not to laugh at?
Right, Ako?
Huh? I am impressed by the fine work she did,
but there's nothing funny about it, is there?
Serves me right for looking to you.
How mean!
So we can just consider this
us making a Net Game Club
and playing net games, then?
We'll all get to play together, right?
That's right! Isn't this fantastic?!
It's amazing, all right. Well, I'll be leaving now.
Hold on, Schwein. Why are you leaving?
Don't call me Schwein!
Listen, I'm fine with just playing
net games as a regular hobby.
Hmph, aren't you the one who said
you wouldn't want a boyfriend,
because it would cut into your login time?
If you extended your playing time by two hours,
just think of how much more
you could earn in one day.
B-But I just want a normal
high school girl life at school...
You'll quickly get outleveled by the rest of us,
our grinding spots will change,
and Schwein won't be able to play with us.
Wouldn't that be a shame?
I don't care what you say, I...
Whoa, check out this rig!
These specs are way too high!
This computer is built only to play net games!
Come to think of it, Schwein,
your PC was fairly underpowered, huh?
That's right! It was a hand-me-down!
You're free to use these, if you like, Schwein.
Ugh, as appealing as that is, it's not enough...
That's dirty! Leave it to Master to play dirty!
Give it up, Schwein.
All right! I'm in, already, I'm in!
But in return, I get to do
whatever I like with her!
Okay then, we can now safely
convene the Net Game Club.
But Master, why did you go to
the trouble of making this club?
What kind of question is that,
Rusian? For you and Ako.
--For us?
--Huh?
We have to show Ako the difference
between the game and reality.
Isn't that what you said?
Yeah, I did.
The characters in the game and the
people in here exist simultaneously.
If we're to show Ako the difference
between the game and reality,
these are the best circumstances, right?
I get it.
Hmm, I don't think this will change anything.
No, I'm a pathetic jerk.
I'm going to shatter your
dreamlike illusion of me to pieces!
That statement alone sounds pretty cold to me.
Oh, no. I'll prove to you that my love
runs much deeper than that!
--I couldn't ask for more!
--Right!
I am so pathetic!
That just isn't true.
I guess the others aren't logged in yet.
Huh? Rusian?
Long time nyao see!
"I thought net games
and reality were different?"
Nishimura's unhappiness
makes my food taste sweeter--
a meshiuma situation!
Urgh, are you trolling me, you pig?!
Who are you calling a pig?!
I'll stick you like one!
Yeah, exactly like one!