Remember, everyone, this is the final battle.
Котаны, отступать некуда, позади Москва.
Our objective is to capture the fort
and defend it until time is up.
Наша задача захватить и удерживать форт до завершения эвента.
The fort is currently being
occupied by Wallenstein.
На данный момент форт под контролем Валленштейн.
We're taking the fort from them.
Необходимо выбить их оттуда.
Our hurdle is already pretty high.
Час от часу не легче.
No, I don't think that will be a problem.
The fort is probably empty.
Не думаю, что с этим будут проблемы. Скорее всего форт заброшен.
Why do you think so?
С чего ты взял?
Because we heard as much
from him, personally.
Их лидер сам нам сказал при встрече.
Defending is no fun.
Обороняться? Увольте.
We enjoy conquering others who
are desperately trying to defend.
Лучше наслаждаться тщетными попытками сдержать наш натиск.
That's what he said.
Такие дела.
I'm surprised you would go talk
to someone who did that to us.
Странно, что вы вообще пошли на аудиенцию с этим проходимцем.
No, it's just like you two to endear
yourselves to that alpha geek.
Нет, просто кто-то покрасоваться перед этим альфачом.
No, not "you two."
It was Ako who endeared herself.
Никаких «кто-то». Тут только Ако с буферами.
Huh? Rusian, you're the one
who said we should go!
Э? Но, Русиян, это была твоя идея!
So, it will be easy to capture the fort?
Выходит, полдела сделано?
Not necessarily. There will be other
guilds coming after the fort, too.
Не скажи. Не только нам интересен этот форт, там будут и другие гильдии.
Even after taking the fort,
defending it the whole time will be hard.
Даже если захватим форт, нам предстоит держать оборону, что не так просто.
Just like we had it taken from us last time.
Иначе будет как в прошлый раз.
Let me at it, both attacking and defending!
Хоть атака, хоть оборона — мне побоку!
I'll show off the results of my practicing!
Я дрочила как бешеная целую неделю!
The problem is the end game.
Дело за эндшпилем.
They probably...
Скорее всего…
...will be coming again.
…заявятся они.
Mm-hmm.
У-му.
The mighty mercenary guild, Wallenstein.
Великолепная пятёрка наёмников — Валленштейн.
We owe those guys, big time.
Воздадим им сполна.
"LV. 12: My net game wife is a girl online!"
[ЛВЛ. 12: Моя вайфу на самом деле девушка!]
Huh? Isn't Phine-kun here?
Хм? Фине-кун не пришёл?
Apparently, it's his child's field day.
Внязапно, его избили цыгане.
Huh? So that means that I'm the only tank?
Э? Т.е. кроме меня танковать некому?
I am sincerely grateful that so
many of you have come together
Всех тех, кто откликнулся на наш призыв и пришёл сюда сегодня,
in response to our request.
благодарю от души.
We, the "Alley Cats,"
which is to say, stray cats,
Мы «Бродячие коты»,
другими словами — драные неки,
along with Nekohime's Elite Guard,
will, for the duration of this fight,
и «Элитная гвардия Некохимы»
на время сражения станем
be the Stray Cat-Princess Elite Guard!
Элитной гвардией драной Неки!
How come?
Я ливаю.
We stand with Nekohime-sama!
Некохиме-сама мы за вас!
You mean, "Alley Cats" means stray cats?
«Бродячие коты» это типа драные неки?
You didn't know that?
Сама как думаешь?
Siege warfare is now commencing.
«Осада крепости» началась.
All right, I'm getting fired up!
Ну всё, понеслась!
Oh, yeah!
Ща!
Let's do our best, Mu-tan!
Не подведи, Му-тан!
Let us carve our victory on the dawn's horizon!
Впишем же наши имена капсом в анналы логов!
Stray Cat-Princess Elite Guard, move out!
Элитная гвардия драной Неки, выдвигаемся!
The enemy got there first!
There are over thirty of them!
Враг уже там! Не менее 30-ти человек!
Emperor Sword, huh?
Меч Империи?
The group that we defeated the last time.
Те, с которыми мы имели дело в прошлый раз.
Wait, you're here, Yuyun?
Ты тоже тут, Ююн?
Yes, I am!
Представь себе!
They got in before us.
Just as planned.
Switch from defensive posture
to attack! Bring down the fort!
Всем переключиться на атакующий режим! Форт будет наш!
We'll get the siege weapon ready, okay?
Осадные орудия к бою?
Do it.
Офк.
Fire!
Пли!
Charge!
В атаку!
For our Nekohime-sama!
Во имя Некохиме-самы!
Drive the enemy out!
Ляжем здесь костьми!
Get them, get them! Grant me victory!
О да, о да! Всё ради победы!
Damn... we can't seem to break through.
Ёпт… Похоже, мы тут увязли.
Aren't we a little short on teammates?
Хули нас так мало?
Gi moving out!
G готов!
Infantry gi moving out!
Керри-G готов!
Decoy gi moving out!
Суппорт-G готов!
Transport gi moving out!
Транспорт-G готов!
That's a lot of gies.
Фулл-хаус-G!
We don't need gies at the moment!
И на кой ляд они нам сдались?
We don't have enough material!
Нужно больше золота!
We need to have more people
on the material-gathering team!
Реквестирую ещё людей на сбор ресурсов!
There are too many gies
and not enough teammates!
Да вы там угораете што ле?
Sette-san overdoing things
is working against us!
Сетте-сан, это уже Эребор!
Damn! We don't have enough tanks!
Ёпт! Один танк в пати не воин!
We can't get through!
Не прорваться!
If we could just get an opening for a second...
You want to make an opening?
Okay then...
Тогда…
Everyone, hold on just a little bit longer!
Котаны, продержитесь ещё чутка!
The Black Magician is on his way now!
Чёрный Властелин спешит на помощь!
Oops, wrong crowd.
Ой, мисчат.
What was that open chat for?
Ты чего в паблик орёшь?
Nishimura-kun, you guys say something, too.
Нисимура-кун напиши тоже что-нибудь.
Not true! They aren't coming!
Фейк! Он не придёт!
TMW isn't coming.
Покрепления не будет!
No problem!
Ложная тревога!
Hmm... Okay, Akane! Now! Go on!
Хмм… Так, Акане, дело за тобой!
Huh? Now?
Э? Прям щас?
Hurry!
Живее!
--There's no way they're coming!
--Way too implausible!
— Какой Чёрный Властелин?
— Хорош втирать.
Doesn't even rise to the level of a bluff!
За кого вы нас держите?
You're mine! Take this! Finishing move!
Ну всё!  Вы огребаете!
Ran! Ran!
Вжух! Вжух!
Ran-ran! Ran!
Вжух-Вжух! Вжууух!
As long as I can ran-ran, I don't care if I die.
Вжух-вжух и gg wp.
As long as I hit twice, I'm ahead!
Один удар — один фраг!
Such is my Akane style!
Таков стиль моей игры!
See? You got through, right?
Здорово мы их?
How did you know the timing of their replies?
Откуда ты знала, как отреагирует противник?
Rusian, I'm scared of her.
Русиян, бежим отсюда.
Rush the front line! Push through!
Оборона прорвана! Рашим!
Come back for the stronger opponents later!
Сильных оставьте на потом!
Make sure to pick off the weaker ones first!
Выносите мелочь в первую очередь!
That's brutal.
Жывотные!
Take that!
Пиздых!
I'm putting it in.
Вставляю.
Fort Cantor has been captured by Alley Cats.
Форт Кантор захвачен гильдией «Бродячие Коты».
--All right!
--We did it!
— Отлично!
— Збс!
I'm a hundred times happier than last week!
I know!
Keep on your toes.
We'll be defending right away.
Twenty minutes left.
If we can defend this...
All forces, charge!
--Huh?
--Charge?
Ako!
Eyes on me!
Why is our mage out front?
Remember, Ako!
Watch only me!
W-What do you mean by that?
I mean this!
Stop them!
That much stamina...? W-What's going on?
Ako!
Right!
Extra Damage!
This...
This... is my attack power!
What can I say?
Ako, good job.
Huh? Right!
Timing-wise, I think my
Extra Damage got in, too.
Sensei, take a hint.
Ten minutes left.
Just about time.
Here comes the real fight.
Enemy attack!
What's the enemy breakdown?
There are five of them!
It's Wallenstein!
They're here.
I knew you would be coming, Bats.
However, we're not giving this up.
Repel them! Show them what we're made of!
Oh, yeah!
Rusian's squad, maintain the
2nd defensive line with your lives!
Roger!
Schwein's squad, stand by
in the inner courtyard!
If they get inside, launch a surprise attack!
Yeah!
Here they come. Fire!
Schwein!
Let's go, you guys!
Hmm...?
They know what you're up to!
No news to me!
Damn! This is hopeless after all.
It's not... hopeless!
Hey, those White Elixirs go for 500K each!
How many did you just drink?
I'm not fooling around here, either!
Ran-ran!
That's all I've got, huh? I'm not much use, am I?
Don't be absurd. You're our MVP.
Two more minutes?
Time and enough to spare.
You bastard...
Well, do your worst--
Yoo-hoo, Bats!
Yikes, we used our skills!
Niaow! Charge!
Bats, when people sacrifice themselves,
this is how they do it.
Shut up, you scrub!
He's stunned!
Two men down! Three to go!
Two to go!
I'm done for!
--Why, you...!
--You'll pay for that!
Hi there.
Tank-on-tank, this is going
to be a wet noodle fight.
Oh, that's right!
My stun is about the only
thing that can stop Bats!
Damn it!
Nishimura, hurry!
You're the only one who
can protect the crystal!
I know, but this guy is...
Don't worry. I'm still here.
One more minute, and one more person.
Ha-ha, this is too easy!
That chat now leaves you 55 seconds.
Your typing speed isn't that great.
Master!
Huh?
Huh? Master, you're alive?
No way, hold on! You can't
possibly be doing that!
Come here a second, Koro!
This one's trouble. Throw a stun, quick!
I won't let you!
Damn!
Watch out, Master!
A stun is coming! Get out of there!
I can't run away! If they get
through here, it's all over!
You'll die!
No, you don't!
Cheep-cheep...
Out of the way!
Well done, Ako!
Nice! Ako, you're tops!
Huh? You're complimenting me,
even though I died?
All right!
Master, come on! You have to win!
Is that all the power you've got, Bats?!
Damn it, die, already! I mean it!
Three...!
Two...!
One...!
Zero!
Siege warfare is now at an end.
You're kidding, right?
TMW has been instated as the lords
of the imperial palace Lodestone.
The Aristocrats have been instated
as the lords of the great citadel Gramberg.
The Cleaning Crew has
been instated as the lords
of the Templar Fortress of Ray Sword.
The Alley Cats have been instated
as the lords of Fort Cantor.
Hooray!
We won!
We did it!
--You see that?
--In your face, Wallenstein!
Right in your face!
Nekohime-sama is victorious!
All glory to our goddess!
You have my admiration, everyone!
We made it!
Well done, men!
Gi moving out!
He doesn't have to.
This fort is now ours!
Hey, are you out of your mind,
what you just did?
What's this, losers weepers?
I did not lose. Every time I hit you,
you used a Drop of Ygg, right?
Huh? Drop of Ygg?
You mean a Drop of Yggdrasil?
The ones that are 10M each?
How many did you drink?
Let's see, I had five hundred
of them before the battle,
and I have thirteen left. That victory
came on surprisingly thin ice, huh?
You drank refresh potions, right?
Taking this castle doesn't even
earn you 5M. What are you, an idiot?
For that matter, where did you
come up with that much money?
That's not an amount you can
typically earn by just playing.
I didn't come up with it from anywhere.
I just sold the items in my
inventory that I didn't need.
That you didn't need?
That still wouldn't raise that much.
All I did was get rid of my mystery box
and premium bonus items I received.
In other words...
...real money.
That's full-blown RMT, isn't it?!
It's not against the terms of use. How rude.
How many tens of thousands did you spend?
I only used one coin.
The hell you did.
Listen, Bats, I'll tell you the truth.
Even if it was in the millions, as long
as it's for my friends, it was one coin!
That's a terrible waste of money.
No, this was the second-most
beneficial use of my money in my life.
This one really is nuts.
But that's okay. I still like you.
Master you endear yourself to weirdoes, too.
That doesn't please me in the least.
Ugh, so it was money after all, huh?
I guess Master really is Master.
--Come to think of it, Master...
--What?
Remember when you said it was the
second-most beneficial use in your life?
Mm-hmm.
Then, what was the first?
Do you even have to ask? The time
I gained my partner here, of course.
How was it?
You charged in and got hacked
to pieces like crazy. Any regrets?
No, I am quite satisfied.
I'm glad I made the effort.
Right? Okay, now we have the actual
culture festival. Hang in there.
Quite busy in here, huh?
Compared to the other clubs,
it may not be a turnout to boast about.
Yeah, well...
Still, for us, this is a shot we can be proud of.
Yo.
Wow, imagine working this hard
for the culture festival.
Don't talk to me like we're friends, would you?
Right, right.
"Yakiton"
Who'd have thought I could ever talk
normally to you like this, Nishimura?
Now you say this? We talk normally in
the club room and while gaming, right?
The game and reality are separate, aren't they?
Here.
Y-Yeah.
Well, you did pretty well all around today,
so here's a fighting-spirit prize.
Isn't grilled pork cannibalism?
Who are you calling a pig?!
Aren't you going to see the displays
in the other club rooms?
I said I wasn't going to, didn't I?
You're going to Ako's anyway, right?
Yeah.
Throw your trash away.
Thank you. Well, see you later...
...partner.
Yo, Nishimura!
You came after all, huh?
You like this too, huh?
I can't take any more!
--Ako!
--Huh? Rusian?
Hey! What good will running away do?!
I know, but...
Come on, come on, go back.
Welcome home, dear.
Listen, that's not what a maid says...
Oh, what's the use? She's not a maid...
She's my wife.
Man, what are Master and the
others doing, not cleaning up with us?
The culture festival was fun, huh?
Right?
What do you say? This regular
school life isn't so bad, is it?
No.
But if you ask me,
that's because you're here, Rusian,
and so is Schew-chan, and so
is Master, and so is this club.
Still, Ako, you really hung in
there for this culture festival.
Yes. I even think so, myself.
You were even the head maid.
P-Please don't remind me of that.
Yeah, but really, you did well.
Then, give me some kind of reward!
All right, anything you want, just name it.
Oh, you just said anything I want, right?
Hold on! By reward, I meant
something from the game!
Big news!
This next update is going to
feature housing functionality!
We're not interrupting, are we?
--Huh?
--O-ho...
Ugh, what are you two getting so
heated up over, all by yourselves?
No, no, it wasn't like that!
Huh?! You said you would do
anything I wanted, didn't you?!
H-Hey! You can't do anything
indecent on school grounds!
It's not that!
I told you, the reward has to be from the game!
It's the same either way, isn't it?!
It's not the same!
The game and reality are separate!
But why?!