You look like you didn't get enough sleep.
Выглядишь так, будто всю ночь вагоны разгружал.
I'll bet you were up late gaming, weren't you?
Клянусь своей пилоткой, играл до поздней ночи.
Yeah, well...
Ну, какбэ…
It's not even 6:00 yet,
Ещё даже шести нет.
but Sensei, you're wide awake, aren't you?
А вы, сенсей, бодрячком.
Back in college, on the wrestling team,
Пока занималась рестлингом в ВУЗе,
we had morning practice every day.
привыкла вставать на тренировку с первыми петухами.
Oh, looks like they're here.
О, вот и они пожаловали.
Morning.
Доброго.
Good morning...
Доброе утро…
Whoa...
Опа…
Ah! No, I was just...
Э! Нет, я тут…
Don't worry about it. I'm just sleepy.
Расслабься. Я просто не выспалась.
O-Oh...
О-ох…
That's everyone, right?
Все в сборе?
Okay then, as of now,
Отлично, тогда
the Modern Communications
Electronic Game Club's
летние сборы клуба «Прогрессивных средств игрового взаимодействия»
summer camp is underway.
прошу считать открытыми.
The goal of this camp is to build up our
strength for the purposes of net game play.
Цель поездки: прокачать тело и дух, чтобы задница в рейдах не затекала.
As such, for the duration of the camp,
А ещё, на время сборов,
connecting to the net is prohibited.
выход в сеть под запретом.
Huh?
А?
It will be called...
Назовём это…
"The 24-Hour No-Net-Connection Camp!"
«Суточный Единый Разрыв»!
"LV. 07: I thought if I went to the beach,
I would become a normie?"
[ЛВЛ. 07: Думал, отдых у моря сделает из тебя нормалфага?]
The net is off-limits during the camp?
Запретить пользоваться интернетом во время поездки?
Mm-hmm.
У-му.
Is this to disconnect her from
the net and make her realize
Хочешь отрезать её от сети, чтобы она ощутила
that her marriage in the game
is different from real life?
разницу брачной жизни в игре и реальности?
No, it's not that.
Нет, не совсем.
The reason Ako is so absorbed in net games
Реальность так довит на Ако
своим несовершенством,
is because she's tired of a reality
that isn't going her way.
что она повернулась к ней задом,
а к виртуальным мирам передом.
Isn't that right, Rusian?
Согласен со мной, Русиян?
Y-Yeah.
Д-да.
But if that were turned around,
Надо повернуть её обратно,
she'd look forward to a reality
where things do go right for her.
показать ей, как прекрасен этот и мир, пробудить в ней интерес.
Hmm, you may be right.
Хм, может быть и так.
Which means that if she spends
the summer with the rest of us,
План такой: тащим её с собой на пляж,
enjoying her youth by spending the
summer like a normie high-school girl,
там она светит арбузами,
будто нормалфаг какой-то,
including a proper love confession
under the perfect circumstances,
а ты душишь в себе омегу
и признаешься ей в любви.
things are certain to go well.
Идеально. Лучше не придумаешь.
B-But what is a proper confession
under perfect circumstances?
Я видел порнофильм,
который начинался точно так же.
One made while watching
the sun setting into the sea?
Мне сделать это на берегу
моря под закатным солнцем?
Or maybe while looking up
into a sky full of stars?
Или подняв указующий перст в звездное небо?
Where we're going for camp,
there's an environment for anything.
У тебя будет предостаточно
возможностей её завалить.
The rest is up to you, Rusian.
Тебе решать когда и где, Русиян.
Up... to me...
Мне… решать…
I just have to declare myself normally,
like a normal high-schooler,
Обычное признание обычного человека,
and get a normal "OK" from her, that's all.
обычное «ну ок» в ответ, делов-то.
Goshoin-san, how much was this cottage?
Come on, how much? Come on.
Госёин-сан, чо-почём за хату?
Чо-почём? М?
Um, could you not grill your student
about the price of her cottage?
Хм, может не стоит такое спрашивать у своих учеников?
Y-You're right. I should mind me-own business.
Н-няверное ты прав. Мяуня не касается.
It's like a hotel, isn't it?
На три звезды потянет.
So, after we drop off our bags, then what?
И? Что будем делать после
того как расчехлимся?
Clean? Air out the futons?
Уборка? Проветривание матрасов?
They've been told we'd be coming today.
О нашем приезде было известно заранее.
The caretakers will have already handled that.
Горничные уже обо всём позаботились.
Well, that was easy.
Где они теперь?
Hey, this isn't what a club camp
is supposed to be, is it?!
Эй, слышь, так дела не делаются.
Isn't cleaning and making the beds up
something you would usually do?!
Какой лагерь обходится без уборки
и подготовки койко-мест?
That's what makes it a
legitimate camp, isn't it?! Right?!
Без этого всего лагерь — не лагерь. Вы чего?
A private beach? For real?
Частный пляж? В натуре?
Rusian!
Русиян!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Заждался небось?
U-Um... if you stare at me too long...
Э-эм… Ещё чуть-чуть и я забеременею.
S-Sorry! So, um... where are the others?
П-прости! А… где там остальные?
They're going to take a little longer,
so I came on out first.
Кто-то сжёг их купальники, а я не стала ждать, пока они сошьют новые.
Rusian, I thought you'd be
lonesome out here by yourself.
O-Oh, okay.
Y-You don't have to be so bashful.
When I picked out this swimsuit, I was all for it,
but now that it's actually time to wear it,
all of a sudden, I feel shy.
It's all right.
Huh?
You look damn cute.
You can feel proud of yourself.
Thank you very much.
Sure enough, you came out here first!
Hmph, my plan to have all three of us
show up together in swimsuits...
...give Rusian a nosebleed...
...and send him running
to the restroom is ruined!
No, no nosebleeds, and no running off.
By the way, Ako, have you put on any sunblock?
Huh?
With skin as unhealthily pale as yours is,
if you spend the day out in the sun,
you'll be in pain for a week.
Eh?
From a sunburn that
makes it hurt to even move.
Eep...
--Just hold still!
--That tickles!
I have to say, you're squishy all over.
Hmm, by the looks of it, Rusian,
you don't have any on you, either.
Huh?! I-I don't really--
No need to be shy. I'll rub some on you.
--No...
--And I will lend a hand!
--Whoa--
--I want to apply some, too.
Hold on!
N-No! Not there! Not there!
No more!
I'm defiled... I'm so defiled...
Whew!
That big a deal, Rusian?
You should be thanking us, instead.
Looks like everyone is ready.
Okay, let's all get to it!
Yeah!
Yeah...
Whoo, that was good swimming.
That was good diving.
That was nice floating.
Great floating.
You know, you look like you're
all done, but it's still midday!
Hmm?
And another thing--why don't
you all play together?!
Huh?
The thing is...
It's like this.
Imagine there's a net game
with a new map installed.
O-Okay...
So then, we all go to the new map together.
But then, once we go in,
we immediately split up.
Why is that?
The important things about a new map are...
...how good the EXP is for solo grinding...
...whether or not there are any rares...
...and how high the death rate is.
Huh... and...?
After we make our rounds, we join up again,
and finally, we gauge
our collective productivity.
We do what we want to do individually,
then come back again when done.
That's our pattern.
Is that what the new normal is now?
I don't know about that,
but it's what's normal for us.
Mm-hmm.
Now that you've got us started,
I want to play some net games!
The net is off-limits during our camp.
Yeah, I know, but...
I'm done playing around in the sea.
I'd like to go sleep in the cottage.
I don't believe you people.
This is a summer camp! We're at the beach!
How can you not play together
and glisten with the sweat of youth?!
The sweat of youth?
We're not very good with that.
Good or not, if you give up,
you'll never get anywhere!
Give it a whirl! You can do it if you try!
Why won't you give it your best?!
Er, but if we try a net game
and don't like it, we move on to--
Reality and the game are separate!
Just do it! Do it, I say!
This is an order from your advisor!
Master!
Okay! Go left! Right! Left! Right!
Now up! Up! Down! Down!
Then go B! A!
Hey, that's the God Mode command!
Hmm?
Okay, all done.
Mm-hmm.
Hey! What is this?!
Ah... the sweat of youth
can be nice once in a while.
Oh, yeah. I'm supposed to
act out my youth at this camp,
and tell Ako...
Rusian!
Русиян!
W-W-Wha--?!
You don't mind if I join you, right?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
A little longer! Just a little longer!
It was just getting good!
--Absolutely not! What were you thinking?!
--She saw me...
Let's BBQ!
Устроим BBQ!
You mean barbecue, right?
Let's BBQ!
Oh, she's having it her way.
Um...
Why haven't those ingredients been prepped?
What does that mean?
All right. I'll see what I can do.
I want to try, too!
We don't have time, so...
I got snubbed by Ako...
She implied that I'd be in the way...
--Woo-hoo!
--Wow!
--This looks delicious!
--This is so good!
Ah, that was good eating!
It was delicious, wasn't it?
Still, I can't believe that except for you, Ako,
we were devoid of any cooking skills.
It's a good thing you were here.
Take my bad self's Burning Edge!
Is she acting out a broadsword skill?
She is swinging it around, huh?
That's dangerous, though.
Hey, you!
Oh, around and around she goes.
Coaching complete!
Looks like it's just about time.
What's the matter, Ako?
Huh? Oh... I'm sorry. I didn't mean to cry.
Somehow, I'm just so happy.
I didn't think I would ever
get to spend a day like this.
So I'm so happy, it doesn't seem real.
But for some reason, I feel sad, too.
Ako...
Um...
Thank you very much.
What for?
I mean, Rusian, if it weren't for you,
there's no way I'd be in a place like this.
And if it weren't for you, Ako,
I'd never be here, either.
Then it's a good thing the two
of us are together, isn't it?
Yeah.
Ako... Ako, I...
...love you.
And I... And I... really love you, too... Rusian.
We really do make a great
married couple, don't we?
Despite all that, it didn't work.
I thought that if we cut out the net
and put on a normie summer,
it would work.
She thinks you're a full-blown
married couple in real life, too.
And another thing! After coming this far,
I just realized something...
Married couples are one rank higher
than boyfriend and girlfriend!
No matter what I do, there's no swaying Ako!
It looks like this quest...
...has failed.
Come on, everyone!
It's lights-out time. Hurry up and go to bed.
Okay, we're heading out!
Master, when you say heading out,
are we going someplace else?
Hmm, someplace good.
The Hotel Flores! Starting now,
the Modern Communications Electronic
Game Club's true camp begins!
What the...?
This hotel is currently
collaborating with Legendary Age.
They're doing it with a hotel?
Someone must have finally been
turned over to final collections.
Ah! They have Poaring King!
He's so fluffy!
Heh, Segawa, are you sure
you don't want to go, too?
O-Of course I'm not going to!
I finished checking us in.
Here's your key.
What's this?
Your token to use for the event.
It's so cute!
As a result of cutting ourselves
off from the net for one day,
our net game powers have
been elevated as never before!
By using these token passes...
...and logging in over there, we will
begin the much-anticipated event!
I see, so that's what these token passes are for.
After that, we just log in with
our own ID and password as usual?
Huh? Hey, no peeking. It's bad manners.
Huh? But why not? A husband's
password is also a wife's password.
Nobody thinks that.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh, it didn't take my password, I guess.
You must have typed it in wrong.
That's because you butted in, Ako.
It took it this time.
Wow, it's laid out like the real-life hotel.
It's a map that only
event participants can enter.
"Welcome to the Legendary Age
Select Collaborative Event.
There are many bonuses set aside
for all of the participants.
Begin by going to the Hotel Flores'
1st-floor restaurant."
Oh! There are item names written
on the side of the menus!
Does that mean if you order them,
you get that item in the game?
That's right.
That's nefarious! It's nefarious, but...
...I want some strength-buffing items!
Huh, so if you take the code on
the card you get with the check
and enter it into the game,
you get that item?
Oh, there's something written on the back.
"The same bonuses are waiting
for you in the 1st-floor gift shop."
Why did you buy so many boxes
of gingerbread cookies?
I can't help it, can I?
They had the items I wanted.
Having students go through this event
is giving them a little bit too big
a glimpse of the grown-up world.
We've got more bags now,
so let's split up for now,
and each take a break in our own rooms.
Now that you mention it, we just checked in,
and haven't gone to our rooms yet, have we?
The rooms being used for
this cross-promotional event
are equipped with computers
and internet connections.
Huh? Then does that mean
the items that we got...?
Mm-hmm... That's what it means.
"Rusian, you took your time!"
Where are Schew and Master?
Где Шу и Лидер?
They both said they were going
on ahead to try out their items.
Oh. Well, we should go, too.
Sure, we could do that...
But if you'd like, would you
mind coming to my room?
Huh?
R-Right, of course... When you
said your room, you meant in LA.
Rusian...
Русиян…
Right now, we're all alone
in a hotel room, you know?
I...
Я…
...have been waiting for this for a long time!
Я джва года ждала этого момента!
Rusian...?
Русиян?
Um... What, now?
The two of us are now all alone, aren't we?
So now, I want to exchange some couple's chat.
Hmm... Couple's, eh?
"I thought I was giving up
being a net game husband?"
What's the big idea with the swimsuits?!
Just because it's summer, we don't
have to get into swimsuits, you know!
It's okay! The one you have on is a
status symbol! It's a collector's item!
I will kick your ass!