They're here.
Припёрлись.
This is the server's top-class
mercenary guild, Wallenstein?
Так вот вы какие, наемники из гильдии Валленштейн.
They have all of their PvP equips maxed out.
У них вся снаряга под ПвП заточена в край.
These guys are truly hardcore.
Шишка задымилась.
With these people helping us,
it will be a piece of cake.
С такими-то союзниками мы катку в два счёта затащим.
Hmm, it didn't take long for the
hands-off approach to rear its head.
Эх, понабрали нягибаторов по объявлению, баланс меня побери.
'Sup?
Сап.
Hi there.
Здоров.
Hello.
Приветики.
--Hey.
--Nice meeting you.
— Хай.
— Всем привет.
--Nya!
--We're looking forward to playing with you.
— Ня!
— Приятно познакомиться.
We're looking forward to playing with who?
Приятно ли?..
You're the leader, Bats, right?
Ты их лидер Батс?
And you're your leader?
А ты, значит, их?
Yeah.
Да.
Sorry about this. We can't
form alliances near the forts,
Звиняйте. Гильдиям запрещено создавать альянсы вблизи крепостей,
so even though we're pretty far away,
this is where I chose.
поэтому нам приходится встречаться здесь.
No, that's okay.
Нет, всё путём.
Guild Alley Cats and Wallenstein
have formed an alliance.
Гильдии «Бродячие коты» и «Валленштейн» объединились в альянс.
"LV. 11: I thought we could win
by delegating to others?"
[ЛВЛ. 11: Думал, победишь, загребая жар чужими руками?]
All right, should we
coordinate what we're doing?
Дык вот, начнём с распределения ролей?
Yeah, okay.
А, ну да.
Ako-san, you're the healer, right?
Ако-сан, ты ведь хиллер?
Y-Yes...
Н-немношк…
Is it okay if we split the buffs
so that I handle Concentration?
Не будешь против, если я буду бафать концентрацию?
Can I ask you to handle Sacrament?
А тебе тогда достанется причастие.
Huh? Um... I, uh...
Э? Ну… это…
Oh, do you not know what that is?
М? Рубишь фишку?
Y-Yes, I do know...
Д-да, рублю…
Okay, you handle healing for you five,
all right? I'll cover the rest.
Короче, следи за хелсами своих согильдийцев. А я сделаю всё остальное.
Okay.
Хорошо.
I'll let you handle it, Ako-chan. Good luck!
Ако-тян, флаг в руки, gl hf.
Huh? You're not going to help me?
Э? Вы не будете мне помогать?
This is your club, and as the teacher,
I'm only supposed to observe.
Вообще-то это ваш клуб, а я тут просто для мебели.
Yeah, but...
Вот же ж…
Hmm... Lower level, with that armor?
Хм… Дно в бронелифчике?..
All right, I'll give you applicable
instructions. Do as I tell you.
Будешь на подхвате. Делай то, что тебе говорят.
Okay.
Ладно.
What about my bad self?
Вы про батю не забыли?
Oh, broadswordsman, you can
just charge in and ran-ran around.
Тебя-то? Просто врывайся в толпу и свингуй от души.
Ran-ran? What is that? It sounds like fun.
Свингуй? Что это? Я тоже хочу.
Hmm, in simple terms, he's telling her
to go on a smash skill rampage,
Эм, другими словами, он предложил ей идти напролом
spamming them as much as she can.
и спамить скилл «буйство» по кд.
The idea is that they don't
want me to think too much,
Хочет, чтобы я не напрягалась,
and just swing my broadsword
around like an idiot.
и бездумно махала мечом на 360 градусов.
Okay, fine. I'll ran-ran for you.
Ну и ладно. Отсвингую, мама не горюй.
Don't underestimate the
force of my broadsword!
Двуручником своим я… ПРОНЖУ НЕБЕСА!
R-Right. Good luck.
Ох них… Дерзай!
Yeah-huh!
Хрююююю!
Beyond that, all you really
have to do is tag along with us.
В общем держитесь нас
и старайтесь не высовываться.
Oh? Are you sure that ambiguous
a course is all we need?
Э? От нас больше ничего не требуется?
It'll be fine. That tiny fort will be easy pickings.
Не ссы, Маруся. Захватим вам форт, ты и глазом не моргнёшь.
Okay...
Вот как…
Tell me something, Rusian-kun...
Эй, Русиян-кун…
Hmm?
Чоу?
Don't these people kind of
strike you as being jerks?
Меня одну от этих петушков
наизнанку выворачивает?
--Huh?
--They sure seem like that to me.
— Э?
— Мне тоже в щи противно.
Now, now, let's not speak
too ill of those we've just met.
Полно вам, всего-то пару раз понтов кинули.
That's Fort Cantor?
Это форт Кантор?
They have a defensive line
around the fort's entrance.
По стелсу к нему не подобраться.
Okay, Sette and Ako,
Так, Сетте и Ако,
both of you split up and run down
either side of the fort's walls.
ваша задача: оббежать форт с обеих сторон.
--Huh?
--How come?
— Э? — Зачем?
Just do it; take a lap and come back.
Нет времени объяснять, стартуйте уже.
Let's do what they say for now
and see what happens.
От нас не убудет, давайте попробуем.
Someone's coming!
Вижу двоих!
Ah! I don't like this!
Ай! Хватит!
All right, that thins the ranks
on their front line.
ЗБС, это ослабит их передовые линии.
We're being decoys?!
Мы вместо живца што ле?
Huh? Isn't that mean?
Э? Так нечестно!
Yes, it's mean, but tactically, it's the right play.
Нечестно, согласен, но… тактически это верный ход.
Wait, you, too?
Ты чего несешь?
--He's right.
--Huh?
— Он прав.
— Э?
Our non-combatants are decoys,
reducing the opponent's numbers.
Пожертвовать слабыми юнитами, чтобы отвлечь противника.
As a tactic, it is, indeed, correct.
Весьма эффективная тактика.
But it's not the way that I like to fight.
Но лично мне такой подход не нравится.
Okay, guess we'll undermine
them with this timing.
Так, похоже, шалость удалась.
Let's go!
Наш выход!
O-Okay.
О-ок.
I'll take my frustration out on the enemy!
Ну щас я на них отыграюсь!
The enemy's advance guard is coming out!
Враг вышел из шкафа!
Once they come forward,
they'll be within range of my spells!
Ещё чуть-чуть и они будут в зоне поражения моих скилов!
Don't let them kill you!
Вы там держитесь!
Let me at them! I'll stick them like pigs!
Да без проблем! На шашлык порву!
I've been practicing for this, you know.
Let me show you what I can--
Всю ночь тренировался на кошках. Лёгкого фрага не жди…
Huh...?
:V
W-What just happened?
Что это было?
That was incredible. He knew just
how the opponent would move.
Поразительно. Он будто заранее просчитал ходы противника.
It looks like they aren't hailed
as the best PvP guild for nothing.
Видать, они не за красивую броню прослыли лучшей ПвП гильдией.
Here I thought the ranged
attacks were falling off,
Чуйка подсказывает
and it turns out the archers in
the rear are dropping like flies.
Huh?! All of the Wallenstein
players are going to charge in,
"Bats: No need to stop them
Bats: We're all going in,
Bats: so you can follow in after us
Mizuka: I'm going in, too,
Mizuka: so cover behind me ^~"
so you guys can tag along behind us?!
What the hell?
These guys can handle it without
any help from us, can't they?
Yeah, there's no need for us
to do anything, huh?
Hey, we're still out here...
...running around, you know!
We finally made it.
What's the matter?
Took you long enough.
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Hurry up and place your crystal.
Y-Yeah, I guess so, huh?
Fort Cantor has been captured by Alley Cats.
Well, we're going to head back
to town now and resupply.
All right.
Guys, stay sharp. Now that
we've run them out of the fort,
Emperor Sword will probably
be coming to take it back.
Oh, we'll take care of those guys.
You all stay here and enjoy yourselves.
"Modern Communication
Electronic Game Club"
Ten minutes left.
We conquered it pretty easily, huh?
No real sense of accomplishment, huh?
This isn't the way I'd hoped you would clear it.
This is no fun!
Yeah, but once we get our screenshot,
we'll be all ready for the culture
festival, right? Luckily, it was easy.
Stay on your toes. It isn't over yet.
True enough. Let's focus on building
defenses until Bats gets back--
The alliance between Alley Cats
and Wallenstein has been dissolved.
Huh? Are you allowed to break
an alliance during siege warfare?
If all members of either of the guilds
leave the captured location, it's possible.
Um, if the alliance is broken,
what happens then?
Their attacks will wind up
being aimed at us now.
Th-Then, that means...
It means this!
Nya!
Fort Cantor has been captured by Wallenstein.
That was an easy game.
Siege warfare is now at an end.
Bats, why did you betray us?
It's a lot more entertaining to
turn on you here. A real laugh!
So that's how it is. In that case,
there's little we can do.
I guess it reveals the depth of my ability
in not seeing through to your true nature.
Huh? Oh, yeah...
Guys, we're out of here.
Farewell, Guild Wallenstein.
I expect we will meet again someday.
They're taking this pretty easy.
I thought they would pop their corks.
I've given my students yet
another negative meow-mory!
This is kind of a strange development, huh?
Yeah.
But on the other hand,
it's kind of refreshing, too.
Hmm?
Acting like that isn't really our way, after all,
and it didn't feel right to me to
take over the fort the way we did.
Still...
...it bugs me the way
they took advantage of us.
Everyone else's work on the
culture festival is pretty far along.
Yes, it is.
We're going to have to stick with it.
I suppose so.
Hey, what's the matter?
Rusian, I'm sorry.
Huh?
Oh...
You're apologizing about that siege battle?
I wasn't able to do anything at all back there.
I wasn't able to do anything, either.
So, Ako, you're not to blame,
and have nothing to feel responsible for.
It's not responsibility that's bothering me.
I think it might be regret, instead.
That's the sense I have.
Regret?
Yes. Whenever I do anything,
nothing good ever happens,
so I've come to live my life
so I don't ever do anything.
So it feels like it's been a long time
since I've wondered to myself
why I didn't do anything.
Watching as our crystal was
destroyed right in front of me
without being able to do anything
is something I really, really regret.
That's great!
Huh?
Things are taking a fantastic turn!
H-Huh?
It's like you've leveled up.
Eh? I have?
Yes, you have! Ako, up to now, as a rule,
whenever something was unpleasant or messy
or called for accountability on
your part, you ran the other way.
Mm-hmm.
Now you've gotten so that you
regret having run away from it.
That's major progress, you know.
There's another round of
siege fighting next week.
That's our last chance.
Next time... Next time for sure,
I want to try harder!
I may end up regretting it,
but I'm going to try to regret it!
Yeah! But as long as
we're at it, let's try to win.
You don't want to have regrets, after all.
Right!
"Student Council Room"
Hard at work, Madam President?
Cut that out. It's creepy.
Creepy? You're doing
student council president stuff,
so that's why I called you "President."
Don't talk to me like we're strangers.
As a sign of trust and respect,
feel free to address me as "Kyoh,"
plain and simple.
Okay, fine, "Kyoh."
W-Would you mind not sitting
there in silence, blushing?!
Sorry. That's the first time
any male outside my family
has called me by my first name.
My heart just skipped a beat, that's all.
Well, it doesn't have to.
So, what did you need?
Oh, it's about the upcoming siege battle.
Not to worry. I already have some new gear
that will allow me to keep casting,
even while under attack.
Wait, the price for that stuff skyrocketed
after the siege warfare started, didn't it?!
Also, I stocked up on reflect potions
that take the damage you sustain
and bounces it back to your opponent.
Those are pretty pricy, too.
When you say "stocked up"...
In any event, preparations are moving forward.
I'm the one who came up with
this idea in the first place.
Let me take care of it.
"Let me take care of it," huh?
"Modern Communication
Electronic Game Club"
'Sup, everyone? Huh?
Welcome home, master!
What's up with these?
Remember, we mentioned it before, didn't we?
About the time we went over
to the president's house?
Master had the uniforms they
came up with for that altered,
and brought them in for us.
Hey, that's terrific.
With the maid uniforms, which were
the biggest issue, out of the way,
Ako, your work is just about done, right?
Y-Yes, it is...
Tell me, Ako-san...
W-What is it, Rusian?
You have everything else for
your maid café ready, right?
You are the head maid, right?
The thing is, you see, um...
How is it coming along?
I-It isn't coming along!
Wow! How cute!
You have the maid uniforms ready!
Nice going, Tamaki-san!
But we're sorry! Other than these,
Ako hasn't done a thing
about assigning shifts or
writing serving manuals!
We're sorry! Please help us!
Huh? Wait, there's only a week left!
It's a little late to be telling us.
Oh, Matsui-san, you work, don't you?
Can you bring us serving manuals?
They'll get mad at me if I do.
Oh, but if it's just for school, maybe I can.
Guys!
Come tell us when you can't
take a shift. Everyone--boys, too!
Well, yeah, we have to work
around everyone's schedules.
H-Huh?
You see that? That's the desperate
"Sorry, This Is Too Much,
Somebody Help Me" strategy.
Huh?
If there's something you can't do,
and you don't speak up,
that's when people get mad at you.
If you can't do something,
just say you can't do it at the outset.
B-But...
There are times when it's
necessary to rely on others.
Ako, you do it all the time in the game, right?
Huh?
"I can't do that." "I can't do this."
"Rusian, please help!"
Once you can openly ask for help
from those around you,
you can solve just about any problem.
That's something I learned from net games.
Rusian?
Team with the Alley Cats
during siege warfare, huh?
I'm begging you!
All right, you've got it.
For real?
Yeah. It's not as though
you're complete strangers to us.
Besides...
--...after they slew our Nekohime-sama...
--Help me-ow!
...we cannot allow things to stand!
Guilty!
Now then,
our next stop is here.
An alliance?
TMW is having a hard enough time
holding off Guild Aristocrats
from the great citadel of Gramberg.
I'm sorry, but we do not have
anyone we can spare to help you.
That's not what we're asking for.
We just need the fact
that you are allied with us.
Hmm?
It's not unusual for someone
to struggle to take a fort,
just to have a larger guild
come and attack, just to kill time.
We want you to be a deterrent against that.
I see. No one is dumb enough to
pick a fight with us, just to kill time.
That's what I am saying.
But right now, Fort Cantor
is being held by Wallenstein,
the best of the PvP players.
Even working with the veterans
of Nekohime's Elite Guard,
I think that laying siege itself
is going to be difficult.
It's true that right now,
our chances of winning may be slim.
But we want to throw everything
we can muster against them now!
Hmm...
All right.
We will enter an alliance with Alley Cats.
You're sure?
Yeah. This alliance holds no demerit for us.
Yes, well, there is no merit for you, either.
Sure there is.
It sounds like it could be kind of fun.
Defend Nekohime-sama!
Extra Damage!
Now I have twice the impact!
Nekohime-sama!
Both of you!
You're mine!
Feast your eyes on the even
greater attack power of my staff!
This is just practice, so hold
back a little, would you?
You are coming along quite well, aren't you?
I'd even like to recruit some of you.
Thanks for coming and joining
our siege warfare practice.
Right now, we are allied.
You don't need to be so reserved.
I must admit, though,
that is some amazing equipment.
It must have cost a fortune.
No cost.
Huh? Ridiculous.
An amount uncostly to my lifestyle--
"An amount uncostly to my lifestyle"
so in effect, it's like there's "no cost," right?
Huh?
"My net game wife is a girl online!"
--It's Netoge's final episode!
--So soon?!
You know, I get hit just one time, and I die!
I know! I know!
Believe that my love can save the world!
Thanks for watching, everyone!
Is this the end?!