It happened right after my proposal
to Nekohime-san was turned down.
А вот что случилось аккурат после того как Некохиме-сан отвергла меня.
My friend, Yuyun, said to me...
Мой друг Йуюн изливал мне душу…
My wife, Sara-Sara,
Моя вайфу Сара-Сара
is married to another man
using her other character...
вышла замуж за другого мужика своим альтом.
It's a different character. That's okay, isn't it?
Раз чар другой, то и переживать не о чем.
No, it's not! It's cheating! Cheating!
А вот и нет! Это измена! Измена!
Different people take different
stances on in-game marriages.
Люди женятся в игре по разным причинам.
Sara-Sara-chan probably just
wanted to get the marriage bonus.
Сара-сару-тян скорее всего интересовал материнский капитал.
Even so! I was truly in love with her!
Пусть так! Но я взаправду любил её!
I am through with Sara-Sara.
Сара-сара больше не нужна.
O-Oh...
Нуок…
It's not fair.
Несправедливо…
Huh?
Э?
I won't accept that I'm the
only one who has to suffer.
Не собираюсь страдать в одно жало.
So I asked Nekohime-san to give me the reason
Я тут поспрашивал у твоей Некохиме-сан,
why she rejected your proposal!
почему она послала тебя лесом!
Whoa! You did what?!
Вуш! Ты сделал что?
"1: I'm not interested in
getting meow-rried in the game."
«Во-первых, мяуня не интересуют внутриигровые шуры-мяуры».
"2: It's not as though Rusian is
the only one I'm on good terms with."
«Во-вторых, Русиян далеко не единственный с кем я мяуловалась».
"3: It's not possible for a man
and a man to get meow-rried."
«И в-последних, негоже двум мяужикам жениться друг на друге».
Why did I ever want to
get married in the game?
Какого лешего я вообще вздумал в брак вступать?
Yeah! Marriage can just suck it!
I'm never getting married again!
Сода! Хорошее дело браком не назовут!
Больше никогда и ни за что не женюсь!
Yeah! Me, neither!
Сода! Я тоже зарекаюсь!
We're never getting married!
Поматросить и бросить!
Following that, Yuyun divorced
two other cross-playing characters...
С тех пор Йуюн успел дважды развестись, а давеча…
...and has now married a third time.
…женился в трейтий раз.
So that's what happened.
Вот и вся романтика.
I'm not divorcing you.
От меня развода не жди.
Hmm, that was a quick response.
Хм, уверенности тебе не занимать.
What I was getting at was
people's stances on marriage.
Разговор о том, почему люди вступают в брак.
I love you, Rusian.
Я потому, что полюбила тебя, Русиян.
W-Well, that goes for me, too...
Н-ну, я так-то тоже…
So, what I mean is, not just in the game, but...
Но я сейчас не только про игрушки говорю…
Rusian?
Русиян?
Ah! I'm heading off to bed! Night!
Ааа-ха-ха! Я направляюсь в постель! Снов!
O-Okay. Good night.
Х-хорошо. Спокойной ночи.
"LV. 06: I thought if I declared my love,
I was sure to succeed"
[ЛВЛ. 06: Думал, если совершишь
акт признания, то тебя ждёт успех?]
"...The man gave a great sneeze
and dragged himself to his feet."
«…мужчина от души чихнул и нехотя подобрал сопли».
"Rashomon"
[Расёмон]
Okay then, next, Rusian, you read.
Хорошо, Русиян, читай дальше.
I mean...! N-Nishimura-kun.
Точнее… Н-нисимура-кун.
Tamaki-san, this one looks good.
Тамаки-сан, цени тряпки.
Tamaki-san, isn't this one better?
Тамаки-сан, эти лучше будут.
I think they're both pretty nice.
По мне так одинаково паршивые.
Rusian!
Русиян!
Listen to this, Rusian! It's awful!
Тут такое творится, Русиян! Насилуют!
It's awful!
Меня насилуют!
A-All right. I'll hear all about it later.
Ладно-ладно. Потом покажешь, где они тебя трогали.
"Modern Communications
Electronic Game Club"
[Осторожно, модерн!]
Look at this!
Вы только поглядите!
It's like a whirlwind of smug faces, all saying,
Аттеншвхоры так и кричат с обложки:
"I am the model that reigns supreme
at the top of the school caste!
«Все бабы как бабы, а я богиня.
Bow down before me, commoners!"
Падите ниц, жалкие омеги!»
How does anyone enjoy reading this stuff?!
Почему кому-то нравится эта макулатура?
Hey, don't be so rough with my magazine.
Эй, палехче. Ты мне весь журнал изгадишь.
This is yours?
Так это твой?
That's right. Got a problem with it?
Да. Тебя что-то не устраивает?
No...
Да нет…
All right, Ako, listen closely.
В общем, Ако, слушай суть.
Magazines like this
Подобные журналы
are a kind of "Real-life Offline
Occupational High-School Girl" strategy wiki.
это своего рода вики по игре в «Искусство старшеклассницы Offline».
Wiki?
Вики?
Yeah. Just by reading this,
you get a complete walkthrough
Именно. Читая это ты получишь базовые знания о том
of how to care for your skin, put on makeup,
как ухаживать за кожей, наносить макияж,
the bare minimum in brand names
and celebrities you should know,
необходимый набор терминов из брендов и имен знаменитостей,
and everything else you need to
live as a real-life high-school girl.
и всё такое прочее, чем может быть озабочена старшеклассница.
Now that you mention it,
that does seem important.
А ведь твинанутая блондинка дело говорит.
You bought that?!
Успешное внушение?
In net games, whether or not you
read a strategy guide ahead of time
В сетевых играх многое зависит от того
makes a big difference, right?
прочитала ты мануал ли нет.
But I kind of like playing blind, too.
Но порой интереснее играть вслепую.
The blind play period ended a long time ago!
Эти времена давно прошли!
Right now, in the offline world,
Сейчас,
all that's left are 100% completion parties,
who are only recruiting players
with regular work experience.
I hate end-stage games!
Give in. We have no choice but to
embrace and live "Real-life Offline."
How much do you think I've already
sunk into "Real-life Offline"?
Stop it! Please stop!
Sorry I'm late. Hmm?
Is something the matter?
Not really.
I get it, Ako. I understand just how you feel.
You, too, Master?
I'll talk to Nanako, and ask her
to be a little more considerate.
Anyhow, what are we doing today?
Oh, since we were just talking about her,
let's join up with Sette-san
and do that one quest with her.
Ah, that one?
Aw... Do I have to be with her in the game, too?
Relax, Ako. In LA, your level
is higher than hers.
That's true, but still...
Ah-woo!
Piece of cake.
It is just a beginner's quest
for job advancement.
It's a walk in the park for us.
Go ahead, Sette-san. The glowing thing.
I just touch it, right?
Yep. After that, choose "yes," and--
Gotcha!
Sette has received the divine beast power!
Congrats on making summoner.
Congrats.
Can I conjure up a pet now?
I think you should have "Summoning"
added to your skill table now,
so consider your play style
and choose your pet type--
Okay then, this one!
I choose you! Summoning!
She always decides so quickly.
How cute!
Listen up. Your name is going to be "Mu-tan."
Mu-tan? That's your dog's name at home.
So then, a summoner, huh?
Quite the veteran's job you've selected.
I love animals, so I said, "That's it!"
Huh. Having your pet attack
while you attack from the rear
doesn't fit with my bad self's style.
Heh-heh, "my bad self"!
Would you let it go?
Sorry, sorry! It's kind of hard
getting used to the disparity!
You started the game quite a while ago,
didn't you? Get used to it.
I know, but...
And another thing, you haven't even looked
at that strategy page I showed you, have you?
Mm-hmm. I looked at it,
but didn't understand it.
Whenever I don't understand
something, Nishimura-kun--
I mean, Rusian-kun is the one I ask.
And look what happens as a result!
You hit the wrong button on
that trap and blew us all up!
You attacked that boss monster,
and caused a party wipe!
Sorry.
Watch closely, Ako! It's just like real life!
This is what happens when
you're low-information.
Understood! I will do my best
not to end up like that!
That's a hell of a way to talk about Sette-san.
By the way, you all seem awfully relaxed.
About what?
You know, final exams.
They're coming up soon, right?
Now that you mention it, you're right.
Mm-hmm.
"Off-limits"
And so, the club is in recess until after tests.
The club room is off-limits until tests are over.
Make sure to attend to each of your studies.
Master, you sure are calm.
I've always been an excellent student.
The worst part of it is that it's true.
After we get past final exams,
we have our long-awaited summer vacation.
Do you have something in mind?
Some event, or something?
Yeah, you can look forward to it.
Excuse me!
We're free to log in from home
during exam week, right?
I'll leave that up to your own discretion.
You sometimes need a release
during studying, after all.
Without any club meetings,
our login streak will be broken,
and it means I don't have to go
to school anymore, doesn't it?
No, you have to come. You're critical
on days absent, aren't you?
Yes I am, but since I was only coming
to school for the club anyway,
I can't work up enough steam.
But if you flunk, the club will
be the least of your concerns.
Push through it and come.
Um, I come to school for the club,
but the club is for school... Huh?
--They're both important.
--It's like an endless loop.
Come on, I'll give you a push from behind.
Hang in there! Hang in there!
Please keep pushing me
all the way home like this.
Stop shifting your weight backward.
Still, summer vacation is almost here, huh?
Summer vacation...
Somehow, before it gets here...
--Huh?
--Oh, nothing!
Come on, we've got tests first, right?
Tests...
Are you ready to take your tests?
Ako?
My dream is to be a housewife, so...
How did you do on your midterms?
What was your average?
Don't tell me you failed them.
You did?
What do I do?
If she gets stuck in make-up classes,
I can't declare my love to her...
What are you mumbling to yourself?
Huh?! Oh, you're here, Mizuki?
Yes I am.
But never mind that, Brother,
I need some help with my studies.
Studies?
Help with her studies.
That's it!
Hold on! Brother!
Geez...
Indeed.
Great idea, right?
That way does seem effective.
No way! No way! I think there's
something funny going on here!
Huh?
R-Rusian!
Р-Русиян!
Okay, next. What is the name of the law
where the government allotted
farmland and levied taxes on it?
The Handen Shuju Law.
Correct. Make sure you know
how to write the kanji for it.
Ah! I've had enough Japanese History!
I have kanji dancing around inside my head!
Then we can tackle math next.
My bad self will see to that personally.
I hate math even more!
Don't think you can get past my Icicle Wall.
This is cruel! This is messed up!
This is a game, right?
But here I am, out-and-out studying!
That's because you are studying.
Don't complain. You've got all
of us here accompanying you.
We have to make sure you get
passing grades, no matter what.
Who really cares about the first term?!
I'll just take some make-up courses
during summer vacation!
No, you won't!
The teachers have their hands full
with entrance examinees.
They don't have time to be giving
make-up classes to first-years.
If you don't like math, work on Japanese!
Just a minute, please!
Sensei, if you're teaching me like this,
it already is a make-up class, right?
But I'm not Sensei; I'm Nekohime-san.
Tell me something, Nishimura-kun...
Whoever do you mean?
Rusian-kun. Is Nekohime-san
actually a teacher, or something?
Look, just don't ask. However,
let's all listen to her lesson.
Okay!
When I look at difficult sentences,
it makes my head hurt.
Essays are essential.
Hang in there, Ako.
"Modern Japanese Final Exam"
All right, begin.
Testing days are now over.
Come on, Ako, pull it together.
I had Ako-chan's answer sheets graded first.
No make-up exams or make-up
classes, then? Thank goodness!
This is thanks to all of our efforts.
Isn't that great, Ako?
Then, let's go do some grinding.
Hold on, now. You're still woozy, aren't you?
For now, log off and get some sleep.
Huh? But...
And you're not allowed to skip school
just because tests are over.
All right. I'm going to sleep.
Good night, everyone.
Yeah, good night.
Night!
I have papers to grade, so I'll drop out, too.
I think I'll drop out, too.
Me, too.
Ah, hang on a second, both of you.
I need to... ask your advice about something.
S-So, um...
I want to declare my love to Ako.
How do you think I should do it?
Huh? Lag? Ahem...
I want to declare my love to Ako.
How do you think I should do it?
Don't ask us twice. We heard you.
Then what was that pause for?!
It's just so beyond too late,
we didn't know how to respond.
Yeah, yeah, you really are slow on the draw.
What's up with your timing?
Well, it's almost summer vacation, right?
We won't see each other, except for the game.
Hmm, so you want to make some
youthful summer memories, do you?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, okay, okay, you go
right ahead and do that.
She's right. This is a matter
between you and Ako.
There's nothing that we can tell you.
You two are both cold-hearted!
What if she turns me down?!
So don't declare your love to her.
Well, I don't want that, either...
You're being such a pain.
Given the circumstances, I don't
see Ako rejecting your confession.
She's right. Why not call her right now,
and declare yourself?
She's not going to shoot you down.
Really? You really think so?
That's what I said, isn't it?
Yeah, but... I want to do this right,
not over the phone.
I don't mean to brag, but I've never
declared my love for a girl before.
You two are real-life
high-school girls, aren't you?
Yes, that certainly is true.
Master, you seem like
you'd be popular with boys.
Don't be ridiculous. I have never,
for one single frame, had a boyfriend.
Sorry.
What about you, Schew? Ever had
someone declare themselves to you?
Like I've said, I turned them down.
If you need advice on getting rejected,
I can help you, though.
No, that's okay.
Basically, due to our ages,
no one here has any history with love.
W-Well, we can help think
of some ways to confess
that any girl would appreciate hearing.
Please do!
And over summer vacation,
I hope you will continue to remember
that you are proud students of Maegasaki.
All right, everyone, have a
productive summer vacation.
And bow!
--See you!
--Want to stop somewhere on the way home?
Huh? For real?
Rusian!
Русиян!
Let's go to our last club meeting!
Y-Yeah.
Hey, Tamaki-san.
I'm going to miss not seeing
your beauty for over a month.
Who are you?
Takasaki!
Такасаки!
He went too far.
All right, let's begin the last
club meeting of the first term.
Today is just an ordinary meeting.
There will be no club meetings during vacation,
but Guild Alleycats will
continue as normal, of course.
Everyone be sure to enjoy your
net game life in moderation.
--Yeah!
--Right!
--Okay, okay.
Also...
"Camp"
This weekend, the Net Game Club
will be holding a club camp!
That's so soon.
I can't wait!
Net Game Club Camp?
Net games require one thing. That would be--
well, funds for premium items, to be sure--
but more importantly,
the players' physical fitness!
As such, this camp will be primarily outdoors!
Brace yourselves for this!
Mm-hmm, that's just what young people need!
Naturally, I will be accompanying you.
--Lately, some net games, including LA,
--The beach was on the schedule, too.
--have been rife with account hacking.
--Oh, we'll need swimsuits, huh?
--Everyone take appropriate measures.
--I-I guess so.
If you declare yourself like this,
it's sure to go smoothly.
Good luck to you.
Rusian, what kind of swimsuits do you like?
I assume it's the school's swimsuits, right?
What do you mean, you assume?
Have I ever said anything like that?
No, but as long as I have my school swimsuit,
the boys will all turn into ravenous beasts.
That's an awfully prejudiced idea.
So school swimsuits have
no effect on you, then?
I think, you know, the regular kind is fine.
Hmm...
L-Listen, could we stop here
in this park for a minute?
Sure, okay...
Rusian?
Русиян?
"Apricot's strategy:
Go for broke."
"Go for broke."
Master! Stop screwing around!
Come on, Segawa!
"Create a nice mood
Confess
Jackpot! Cha-ching!"
"Create a nice mood;
Confess; Jackpot! Cha-ching!"
I'll "cha-ching" you. You lousy...
So how do I create a nice mood?
--Huh?
--Oh, nothing.
Rusian, you and I always have
a nice mood going, don't we?
I mean, we are a couple, after all.
Ako...
Hmm?
W-Would you...
Would you...
...be my girlfriend?!
No, I won't.
Why...?
Goodness gracious, however did this happen?
However did this happen?
This is way too much for me.
I'm through with Ako.
And I loved her like crazy, too.
Hmm, despite not taking the
easy potshot we offered him...
...he's in surprisingly good shape, huh?
No I'm not. Ah, I want to die.
Now's my chance. Off to the afterlife.
Hello? Ako?
Nishimura said something to you, right?
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?!
Corpse-kicking? Overkilling?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm...
So, what does Ako say?
Well, um, he said he wanted
me to be his girlfriend.
And what did you say to him?
I said I didn't want that, of course.
I mean, isn't going from wife
to girlfriend a demotion?
"Ako Tamaki"
Either that or it means we're
getting divorced, doesn't it?
There's no way I want that.
There you have it.
In other words, your declaration
fell through, didn't it?
"I thought if I stayed over,
I would become a normie?"
Hold on a second. When it comes
to advice on relationships,
I'm the best one to consult, aren't I?
Why didn't you ask me?
Nah, Akiyama-san, I couldn't.
Why not?!